Londoners will have to make do without the sound of Big Ben for a while.
伦敦居民将不得不在一段时间内忍受没有大本钟钟声的日子。
After 157 years of almost uninterrupted service, the famous London landmark is worn out and needs repairing.
在历经157年几乎不间断的运行后，伦敦这座标志性的大钟已经磨损，需要进行维修了。
Steve Jaggs, Keeper of the Clock, said: "This project will enable us to give one of Britain's most famous landmarks the TLC it so desperately needs and deserves."
大钟的管理员史蒂夫·贾格斯说：“这个项目将使我们能够给予英国最著名的地标之一它迫切需要且理应得到的悉心照料。”
The Elizabeth Tower, a UNESCO World Heritage Site, houses the clock and is visited by 12,000 people a year.
这座伊丽莎白塔是联合国教科文组织世界遗产，大本钟就位于其中，每年有1.2万人前来参观。
It's said to be structurally sound but water caused damage to its masonry and there's corrosion in the cast-iron roof and belfry and the frame which holds the clock's bells.
据说它的结构是稳固的，但水对其砖石结构造成了损害，而且铸铁屋顶、钟楼以及支撑大钟钟体的框架都出现了腐蚀情况。
It all needs fixing.
这些都需要进行修复。
Work will also help to bring the building up to modern health and safety standards.
维修工作还将有助于使这座建筑符合现代的健康和安全标准。
It will have a lift installed to make it easier and quicker to evacuate an injured person and give access to disabled people who can't climb its 334 steps.
将安装一部电梯，以便更轻松、快捷地疏散受伤人员，并且允许那些无法爬上334级台阶的残疾人进入。
And at a time when energy efficiency is a concern, the lights which illuminate the clock dials and the belfry will be replaced by low energy LEDs.
在人们关注能源效率的当下，照亮钟面和钟楼的灯将被低能耗的发光二极管所替换。
Work, with an estimated cost of £29m, is set to begin early in 2017 and is planned to take three years.
这项预计耗资2900万英镑的维修工作定于2017年初开始，计划耗时三年。
The clock will be silent for only a few months though and might come back to life in very special occasions.
不过，大本钟只会沉默几个月，并且可能会在非常特殊的场合再次敲响。
The name Big Ben originally referred to the 13.5 tonne Great Bell within the tower, but ended up being used for the clock and tower too.
大本钟这个名字最初指的是塔内重达13.5吨的大钟，但最终也被用来指代这座钟和这座塔了。
The clock stands 96m above the Houses of Parliament.
这座钟位于英国议会大厦上方96米处。
It was designed by architect Edmund Beckett Denison and began keeping time on 31 May 1859.
它是由建筑师埃德蒙·贝克特·丹尼森设计的，于1859年5月31日开始报时。
Surely it might be our turn to give this famous symbol of Britain some time to rest and recover.
当然，现在也许轮到我们给这个英国著名的象征一些时间来休息和修复了。